All right, here we go.
Hello everyone. It's Michael Jacob with
Unleashing Intuition Secrets of Ian
Trotier back again with High Stakes
Stakes Treason. Uh and we have another
guest, CIA whistleblower John Kiriakou.
Is that Or Kiriakou Is that right?
>> Kiriakou. Kiriakou. All right, Kiriakou.
I've
That's a great Greek name. I love it. Uh
so we're we're going to let John
introduce himself a little bit. He's got
a phenomenal background.
I worked in the CIA and I I had I think
he's an amazing guy from the stuff he's
been telling telling me so far. So we're
going to talk about uh
uh
John Brennan and we all have you know
dealings with him and we we're going to
basically dime him out. So John, give us
a little bit of about your background.
Sure. I'm John Kiriakou. I spent 15
years at the CIA. The first half of my
career in analysis, the second half in
counterterrorism operations. I was the
chief of counterterrorism operations in
Pakistan after 9/11. Finished my career
at the UN.
And then um
blew the whistle on the CIA's torture
program which came back to haunt me
later. I I went on to be the chief
investigator on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee. Uh but then was
arrested um
under the Obama administration uh at the
at the insistence at the demand of John
Brennan.
I proudly served 23 months in a federal
prison. I would do it again today if I
had the opportunity. I have zero
remorse.
Um I'm glad I did it.
John Brennan was a was a criminal. I
think we're all going to end up agreeing
on that today and somebody had to say
something.
So um
since being released from prison 11
years ago,
jeez, I've written nine books. I teach
at two universities. I've got some
podcasts. I've got a TV show called The
Whistleblowers where I talk to other
whistleblowers, mostly national security
whistleblowers around the world.
And I'm happy to join you guys tonight.
Yeah, it's great. Ian, give us a little
bit of background about your book and
again.
Yeah, so Michael, appreciate being back
on being back on and it's
great to be joined by by John.
John was a a guest of Discussion of
Truth, the podcast I started in Miami
back in 2016. Probably back in 2018,
John. I I you
>> so. And one of the early guests on that
podcast and
Michael, just so you know, the origin
originally I approached Mr. Kiriakou
because of his whistleblowing against
the waterboarding
during the Bush administration and and
and those efforts. Now the background
regards to how it how how his
testimonial and experience ties into
High Stakes Treason is as viewers may
know by now and certainly the three of
us know is that
High Stakes Treason lays out a criminal
scheme
that was conducted by the former head of
the CIA while he was serving as a senior
advisor on the security under Barack
Obama just to fraud the American people
and allow terror events to happen on
Americans
and in the homeland and the NATO ally.
That sums up pretty much what what what
what transpires and is laid out in High
Stakes Treason. Now
General Michael Flynn was a initial
person that I approached to write the
forward
to this to this book. John
followed that.
Flynn's schedule got busy but but John
said he'd he'd write the forward. And as
we know Roger Stone because of the
the kind of the the political awareness
that he has over the the past 50 years
has written that main forward but
just as important are the other two
forwards, the one by Brooks Agnew and
and former speech writer for Alan Keyes
and of course one by John Kiriakou. And
we are very fortunate to have Kiriakou
with us because
because much of the as you you just just
heard, much of the
the history that John had after he was
being he was assaulted and and and
blamed for being a criminal and thrown
into jail into prison.
This had a lot to do with the
malfeasance and the character of this
this admitted communist John Brennan.
So that's what we're going to lay out
today, I believe Michael for your
viewers is that they understand exactly
the impression that this character
became the head of the CIA under Barack
Obama
had on Kiriakou's
stalwart
career serving the American people. And
of course
that threads into the contents of of the
book. But let me briefly mention
Zbigniew Brzezinski because if we go
back and John will be familiar with the
Analysis Corporation. If we go back to
when Mr. Brennan was a student at the
University of Texas Austin and he had
voted for Gus Hall that communist
candidate for for for US presidency was
an introduction to
Zbigniew Brzezinski around that time. I
don't have an exact year
that threads in to that of Barack Obama
in the early '80s because the three of
them seemingly um
in in 2008 um in 2008
there was critical information on the
passport that was scrubbed by John
Brennan.
That's the Barack Obama passport between
the time that Barack Obama, Michael
spent at Occidental College in
California and Columbia University
Columbia University in New York, he
spent over a year in Pakistan. The
question is what did he do in Pakistan?
Why did he exactly go to Pakistan? And
why did John Brennan use the Analysis
Corporation
and those tools to go in and scrub vital
information off of that passport during
that time that he had in Pakistan and
what were the contents? We still don't
know that were on Excuse me, they were
on on that passport.
So I'll just insert that as we proceed
here but that is exactly what what we'll
be laying out here
during during this conversation. So
thanks for having me back on.
Yeah, fantastic and you know, for John,
I I did a little time in
the CIA with
>> [clears throat]
>> GRS
about about 13 years and I spent some
time in Iraq, Afghanistan,
Pakistan a lot of a lot of time in
Pakistan. So very very curious to what
your thoughts are on some of those areas
and why was Barack Obama in Pakistan for
a year? What the heck?
I can't even begin to speculate why in
the world he would be in Pakistan. Yeah.
At a time when
we were actively
uh
arming the Afghan Mujahideen, fighting
the Soviets. I mean, it was a legit war
zone. There were important things taking
place.
I can't even begin to speculate what in
the world he would have been doing
there.
Hm. I can tell you a lot about John
Brennan though.
I mean, the first
Let's get into that. But my but the
first the first thing that comes to my
mind here in regards to Pakistan has
exactly to do what you're talking about
in the Mujahideen. And and this
Let's not forget that that Al-Qaeda and
maybe John you can contribute to this a
little bit but but Al-Qaeda and maybe
Michael you may know this. Al-Qaeda for
from my understanding is actually a name
of a software a terrorist tracking
software. And and and of course it
applies to the the terrorist
organization itself. So my my question I
haven't looked at this
I haven't looked into this. My question
is perhaps that's somehow and let's not
forget that the the Analysis Corporation
was created in 1990 as a result of
tracking
that when Soviets pulled out of
Afghanistan tracking and creating that
database to track terror terror
movement.
And so the question in regards to the
passport, where's where's where's this
overlapping? How does it have to do with
Obama's father, right? He was in Kenyan.
And he's studying in the US on on that
student he was a student visa.
How does that have to do even the mother
mother threads in. A lot of sources say
that she was also used as a CIA asset.
Is there somehow an involvement used to
cover up kind of the origins of travel
of Does it Does it thread in somehow to
the the birth certificate controversy at
all? That's
the question.
It's possible, certainly. It's it's
possible that that his mother could have
been an asset. It's possible that his
father and or his stepfather
could have been assets. I mean, goodness
knows they were
they were well placed
to be to be assets.
Yeah. And and God knows he's never
answered those questions. Obama himself.
Right.
We have we have something interesting
developing that Mandelson, Lord
Mandelson and not to not to paint too
broadly because I think we should zero
in with with John Brennan here in this
conversation but but Lord Mandelson so
so so
so so so John Brennan
John Brennan has recently
testified to members of the UK
Parliament. Were you guys aware of that?
No. No, that's that's news to me. Yeah,
this happened
just a couple weeks ago, I believe. I
don't have the exact date but he he went
over to the UK and we know that Obama
has been going back and forth. I don't
know if you knew that but Obama has been
going back and forth Uh to United
Kingdom and
and return to the US. But John Brennan
went over and testified in regards to
surveillance,
security
to to members of the UK Parliament. Now,
after that testimonial, non-related
perhaps, but perhaps related was a
member of Parliament being
resigning
for for information that he gave to
Epstein. Uh
over over a decade over a decade ago.
So,
there's there's certainly ties. I I
don't know
any any any ties between Epstein and and
and and and John Brennan.
I certainly don't
>> an indirect one yesterday. You did? I
did. Yeah. So,
I went I went to the DOJ website
yesterday and I searched for uh
Well, I searched for a bunch of things.
CIA
was one of them. And um
And one document popped up.
And it was an email from Kathryn
Ruemmler, who was the uh
the uh
deputy White House counsel during Obama.
And
Kathy Ruemmler, who's now the general
counsel for Goldman Sachs,
she sent a one-line email
to
Jeffrey Epstein saying this.
Here it is.
John Brennan gave me the CIA agency
medal, the CIA's highest award, this
morning. How cool is that?
Why
in the name of God
would John Brennan give the White House
counsel
the agency's highest honor, which
Michael, as you know, is usually
given posthumously
for people who have given their lives
in the line of duty.
Yeah.
Yeah, I had a couple buddies that did
that. Had got that
>> Yeah.
As did I. Two of my colleagues in CTC,
Mike Spann and Helga Boes.
Well, wow.
>> Both killed in action in Afghanistan.
Yep.
That's how they got their medals.
I don't know why she got her medal,
unless
Well, you you remember I'm sure the the
Tuesday morning kill list meetings that
Brennan initiated at the White House
during the Obama presidency, where he he
would convene this group of people to
come together, decide who to kill that
that week. The assignments would go out,
the teams would fan out around the
world. They would kill whoever they were
assigned to kill and then come back for
the next week's meeting. All I can
speculate is that she was the
White House representative, cuz there
had to be lawyers involved. The CIA
general counsel was in on that meeting.
And I'm wondering if uh
if that's what he did.
I don't know.
Yeah.
>> his hands in in everything, literally
everything. I think is is probably my my
most succinct point. He had his hands in
everything.
So, uh tying this together a little bit
here. Uh when I was in um Peshawar,
uh we were working with a the doctor
that would eventually lead us to uh
Osama bin Laden.
Uh and
>> Who's still in prison in Pakistan.
>> in prison. Yeah, that's a very good
point.
So, uh John Brennan, who was like the
national security deputy national
security advisor during Obama's time
frame. Obama was very very uh involved
in what we were doing
uh during that time frame. They had
meetings probably
maybe even every day. He was very
involved. Uh reminded me of the time
when I was in Iraq in the early days
where where Bush and Condoleezza Rice
were every day, you know, pretty much
talking to Ambassador Bremer.
So, they were very very involved. And
then when we, you know, went in and uh
my old team, Red Squadron, went in and
got uh Osama bin Laden,
uh
things things just went off the cliff. I
mean, we got like pulled out of there.
We got shoved into different places. Had
to shut down that base. Uh it was it was
crazy all the stuff that was going on
during that time frame.
Uh and and then we had that that crazy
crash of
uh SEAL Team Six uh Gold Squadron in
Afghanistan.
Everybody's still suspect about what
happened there. Was that some kind of
payback? You know, I don't know. It's
crazy crazy time. So, uh Brennan uh
had been involved in all this stuff.
Uh so, what were your What are you guys'
thoughts?
Yeah, go ahead, John.
Man, where do we even begin? Um
you know what? Let me let me let me
begin by laying a little bit of um
of background.
So, I first met John Brennan in January
of 1990.
He was a GS-15
nobody.
Uh he was the deputy group chief
um in the Office of Near Eastern and
South Asian analysis. He was the deputy
chief of the Arab-Israeli analysis
group.
Big deal.
He worked for a woman named Martha
Kessler. Martha was
was absolutely brilliant. She was She
was arguably the country's leading
thinker on Syria. And she wrote a book
that was so highly regarded that it was
it was mandatory reading for all of us
as we entered the office.
You know, when you were first assigned
in that office, it was called Syria:
Fragile Mosaic of Power by Martha
Kessler.
Martha didn't like John. He had been
imposed on her as as her deputy.
And one day
she he went to her and he said,
"I've been in this job for a long time.
I think I'm ready for promotion to the
senior intelligence service.
And I want your blessing." And she said,
"Not only will you never be
promoted into the senior intelligence
service. I don't even want you working
for me anymore. You're fired."
Well, at the CIA, as you well know, you
can't really fire fire someone. When you
fire someone, you give them 6 weeks to
walk the halls and find a an onward
assignment. And if they can't find an
onward assignment after 6 weeks, then
they their badge is taken, they're
escorted out, and that's the end of it.
Well, the the normal job turnover is in
the summer, right? That's when
everybody's moving from one job to the
other. This was Christmas
six.
And um there were no jobs.
So, he's walking the halls. He finally
finds a job
in the PDB staff, the President's Daily
Brief, giving a briefing
to the lowest-ranking
person entitled to receive one.
Or 94, 96, 94, I can't remember anymore.
The that person happened to be the
director of intelligence programs at the
NSA. His name was George Tenet.
And so, they immediately hit it off, cuz
they're both, you know, alpha dogs,
ugly, pockmarked faces,
chomping on cigars, cheating on their
wives.
They immediately hit it off.
And George had just had a heart attack.
He was barely into his 40s.
And so, he wasn't supposed to smoke. So,
after Brennan would brief him, they
would walk to this little kiosk that
used to stand on the corner of 17th
Pennsylvania Avenue, 17th Street and
Pennsylvania Avenue Northwest across
from the White House.
And they'd buy a cigar, and they'd stand
there and smoke cigars.
Well, George becomes the deputy director
of the CIA.
And
he brings
John with him
and makes him deputy director of the
Office of Near Eastern and South Asian
analysis. Now, he's Martha Kessler's
boss.
And he calls her in on his first day and
he says, "Now, you're fired."
And so, she elected to retire.
Um he was only in that job briefly,
because there was a realignment and he
ended up being named station chief in
Riyadh, Saudi Arabia. Now, this is a guy
who had who had already done 20 or 22
years solely in analysis.
He had never ever served overseas in an
operational position. He had never
recruited a spy to steal a secret. He
had never met with a recruited asset.
Never.
But he's the station chief in Riyadh,
where we know
he oversaw the issuance of visas that
should never have been issued.
He went back to the CIA after And you
know, that's that's normally a 2-year
tour with the option to extend for a
third. Well, he extended for a fourth,
and he extended for a fifth, and then
went back to headquarters as the deputy
executive director of the CIA.
The fourth-ranking
officer in the CIA. Now, he's
everybody's boss.
And um he very much wanted to become
the deputy director for operations.
Jim Pavitt was the deputy director for
operations at the time, and they hated
each other. And Pavitt had more wasta
than Brennan did. And so, Brennan went
to what was briefly called the TTIC, the
Transnational Terrorist Information
Center.
He He wanted so badly to to run his own
agency, any agency of any size. Because
what he really wanted, and he wasn't
ashamed to say it out loud, he really
wanted to be Secretary of Defense.
And so, he took this position at the
TTIC. Later, it changed its name to the
national
counterterrorism center.
And then um
And then he decided to retire.
Well,
in 2007, there was a huge wave of
retirements from the senior intelligence
service
uh because 9/11 was 6 years behind us.
People are starting to wind their
careers down. It's time to go. Well, you
figure there were 100 150 SISers that
retired. Half of them went to the John
McCain campaign and half of them went to
the Hillary Clinton campaign and John
Brennan was the only one that went to
the Barack Obama campaign.
Wow.
>> And then lo and behold, Obama wins the
nomination. So So, Brennan was the guy.
You might recall that as soon as Obama
won in 2009, he named Brennan as the CIA
director. Yeah. And the liberals went
crazy.
How people have forgotten
that John Brennan was one of the the
fathers, one of the creators of the
torture program, which is why he was
denied that job as CIA director from
2009 to to 2000, you know, 13, January
of 2013. It's a mystery to me how people
don't remember that. But progressive
stood up and said, "Absolutely not." And
so, he pulled him back, made him deputy
national security advisor for
counterterrorism.
By 20 By the 2012 election, everybody
had forgotten what a bad guy he was.
And so, when Obama
nominated him nominated him for CIA
director, nobody said a word. And then
the rest is history.
Wow. Who's there? So, the Abu Ghraib
Ghraib was where they had the the the
waterboarding. I I I'm assuming
>> no. Well well before Abu Ghraib, 3 years
before Ghraib, the the agency was
waterboarding people at at the six
secret sites. See Yeah, I I heard that.
>> the world. Some of them were still have
been were active quite some time, but
that's that's interesting. I when I was
in the military, I I went through
escape evasion training and
I got waterboarded. It's not fun. And
it's it's pretty pretty horrific. And I
was doing pretty good at it. They
couldn't make me talk and there's they
told me
you better start screaming or we're
going to make it really bad for you. And
I I figured they probably could. Uh
because you know, the the angle is not
going to get into you. And I was used to
you know, breathing leaky water you
know,
regulators and so forth. So,
uh but yeah, that would be I watched
other people get on that and
it was horrific to watch you know, what
happened to them. And that was
controlled We were had a controlled
environment. I'm sure the guys who were
being tortured not so much.
Wow.
>> each other in training and it was
miserable. Yeah, yeah. Awful.
Not not Yeah, not not something that we
should be doing. Yeah, so I'm glad you
you pushed against that. So, yeah, you
you you got the experience and you're
like, yeah, this is this is BS that
we're doing this.
>> Yeah, this is not this is not legal.
That was the first thing in my mind.
This is not legal. And and we did things
I don't want to get too far afield, but
we did things that in my view were were
way worse than waterboarding.
You know, not just things like sleep
sleep deprivation and cold cell. I mean,
we killed people with those with those
techniques. But there were things that
were never approved by the Justice
Department that we did
with the idea being,
"Who's going to tell?"
Wow. You know? Yeah. The thing was so
highly compartmentalized.
They didn't think anybody would ever
talk. Yeah.
So So, back to you know, John Brennan
and
Obama,
I just pulled up this one little article
where it talks about Obama being there
in 81. He didn't mention it anywhere
else and then he was like a press
conference, he just kind of said it and
then they started doing the
investigative work on that. So, that's
that's interesting that he spent some
time there and then he was involved in
you know, finding Osama bin Laden. I
think we knew he was there for a while.
And they they decided, okay,
let's let's cut him.
And so,
I don't know what are your guys'
thoughts.
Yeah, go ahead, John. I I think that's
right. I think that's right. Or at least
we had strong suspicions. But you know
what? Then I'm I'm going to get a little
bit off topic here.
You you raised the the issue of the
doctor.
Uh the the doctor that helped us locate
Osama bin Laden.
>> When I was on the Senate Foreign
Relations Committee staff
uh in 2009,
um I did a lot of travel in that job.
And uh John Kerry I I was working for
John Kerry at the time. He was the
chairman of the committee. John Kerry
asked me what I wanted to do in terms of
um
investigations. And I said, "Listen,
I I
everybody knew that the only thing John
Kerry wanted in life was to be Secretary
of State.
So, I said, "Listen, I think we I think
we've got a a real hook for something
great here." I told him about the
doctor. I said, "This guy is is a hero.
He's a hero. He handed us Osama bin
Laden.
And the Pakistanis have him locked up on
a treason charge now. He's going to die
in some dank Pakistani dungeon." Yeah.
I said, "Let's go to Islamabad.
And let's bring him back with us.
I said, "You'll be a national hero."
He says, "Write me up a memo."
So, I wrote him a memo. This is who the
guy is. This is what he did. This is
what we should do. There's no downside
to this. The Pakistanis are would be
happy to just be rid of him. He's an
American hero. Bring him back here and
you know, you can get the presidential
medal for him or whatever.
And then Kerry comes back cuz he had
obviously had called
the White House
including Brennan.
Well, it's so controversial.
I don't know. We don't want to make the
Pakistanis angry and
what if we show up and
and they say, "No, we can't do it." I
was like, "Are you serious?"
And so, we never went to Pakistan at
all.
I I did a different investigation. I
took different trips.
But he just didn't want to do the right
thing at all because John Brennan told
him no.
Yeah,
and [clears throat] I'll weigh in a
little bit on that. I I worked I worked
with the doc. He's a really really good
man.
Uh and uh
and we told him
once once he once we do this, you need
to leave. And he's he's like, "No, I'm
going to be a hero
in [clears throat] my country." And uh
that didn't work out so good for him.
Like you're talking about.
Now uh
I remember President I believe President
Trump in his in his first time in
office, he was he was basically
threatening the Pakistanis uh saying he
was going to cut off aid unless they
released him. I don't know. I might be a
little off on that, but they just went
to China and got aid.
It's like, yeah, we'll just go somewhere
else and get it.
And it didn't work out. So, it's And
Trump was was sure that it would happen.
And of course,
as John, you and I know the Pakistanis
there, you can't
you can't guess what they're going to
do. So, they're they're very
unpredictable.
>> Yeah.
Let me let me mention the TTIC, which
which John was was talking about in
regards to kind of the power consortium
that that John Brennan was able to
create for for himself. Now, this is
after 9/11 and the Bush had an executive
order that the TTIC was was created, but
page 112 in High Stakes Treason goes
into and this is a direct quote from
John Brennan. It gives gives
uh uh viewers an an an understanding of
the and I mentioned in the book
CT Intel monopoly. That means a
counterterrorism intelligence monopoly
is what John Brennan was able to create
for himself from the TTIC, which John
had mentioned became known as the the
NCTC,
National Counterterrorism Center. But at
the TTIC, Brennan is stated as saying
this, "The idea that behind the TTIC,"
as I'm reading a quote, "was that we
needed to have some place in the
government where all counterterrorism
information would reside."
The good news and the bad news is that
the TTIC had more access to more
information than anywhere in the
government.
And that was what John Brennan had at
his fingertips. And that is exactly how
we allege he was able to commit these
crimes. And this is why we use the word
treason because he enriched himself in
retaining stock ownership illegally
under the Obama administration of this
company called The Analysis Corporation,
which changed its names and then got
sold to UK financial investment firm
based in Hong Kong
domiciled in Hong Kong CCP. Um and of
course, he allowed these these these
terror attacks
to to transpire. Now,
my question might be for
for John is what thoughts went through
your mind, John, when you came across
the information in the book. And since
you and I have spoken last, not sure if
you've had a chance to go through it a
little bit more or not. But
understanding the contents laid out in
regards to
the Boston Marathon bombing, the
the Abdulmutallab Mutallab bombing
attempt on that flight leaving Amsterdam
for Detroit 2009. And of course, that
attack on the airline This this is
exactly what the power
of your book is.
Um
I I've known John Brennan for 35 years.
I thought I knew that he was bad guy.
I had no idea
the depth of his depravity,
the lengths that he would go to to
enrich himself
the people whose lives he would ruin
in order to keep himself at the top of
the heap until I read that book.
I agree.
>> Until I read that book. Mhm. Listen,
there are a lot of bad guys in
government. We've all encountered them.
This is somebody
whose
dirty deeds are of epic proportions.
And I can't help but to think
that there are so many crimes
documented in the book
that there's got to be something in
there
for which the statute of limitations
hasn't expired. Absolutely.
>> and you and I have talked about this,
Ian. Yeah. Or
Brennan's ongoing
work
to keep his crimes a secret
could constitute an ongoing conspiracy.
Yes.
>> Which means that the statute of
limitations would reset itself every
day.
Yeah. What do you say about that?
>> a I'm not a constitutional scholar, but
this is worth seeking one out.
And and like you pointed out, Ian, and
John, like you described, you know, in
the early like in the mid-90s or so,
there was nothing going on. And you
know,
pretty much they created something and
then we're all involved in this and
there's lots of money that's involved in
this and you know, you really outlined a
lot of this exceptionally well.
Uh so I I looked up the
the 2-minute promise
during two during our President Trump's
2016 campaign. Trump stated he would get
Pakistan to release Dr. Afridi within 2
minutes of taking office arguing that
the US gives Pakistan
substantial aid and unfortunately the
historical aspect of that is that he is
still in prison.
Very very tragic and very You know, the
guy guy's a hero here in America. He
should be walking He should getting that
$50 million
you know, money. I don't know. Maybe
they decided to keep it. They let him
have him so they could keep the money.
That's that's crazy.
Yeah, there's a
there's a and not to not to forget if if
folks heard the first interview that
that that Michael and I had and
Edward Snowden here
and the whistleblowing he did on the NSA
is critical in understanding and then I
know Fox News right now has I'm not sure
who produced that, but it's is he a
patriot or is he a traitor? As far as
I'm concerned, Edward Snowden be a
patriot. This is my personal gut feeling
based upon
what we know through XKEYSCORE and what
was revealed through that and that
Anders Breivik um
googling This is public search. Googling
how to prepare bombs, create bombs,
ingredients for bombs. This is all
public knowledge that John Brennan would
have had and as we allege, he he hid in
coded compartments using his unwitting
analyst Michael Jones. Now, since also
since the last time we've spoken,
Michael, I've introduced my intelligence
source
because yes, I've authored the material.
Yes, I've added to it, but this this all
came to me on a binder and forgive my
lighting uh folks, I can see it's pretty
dark there. I I don't have the best
lighting. I've got a bum ankle at the
moment, so just bear with me on that,
but
um I was given a binder at that 2024
CPAC. That's where that that was the
that was the incubator that created this
book, High Stakes Treason.
And and and and and that came from Intel
source. That came from an American hero
such as the man that is joining us
today. Both of you, of course.
Thank you for your service. Both of you.
But but but the one can concerning High
Stakes Treason would be Mr. John Donovan
and
and Michael, since you and I spoke last,
I got Donovan on the phone
with with Keriakos. So they have now
they have now connected because in the
shadows, if you will, in the background,
it was Mr. Donovan being tipped off to
the malfeasance of John Brennan back in
2011 when he was working with the
private contractor Sci Veyance. And and
and he got fired. He got fired He got
fired by Sci Veyance because he tipped
off the FBI, his former employer who'd
spent over a decade with in in the
Washington DC field office. Sci Veyance
fired him for tipping off the FBI, which
did nothing, of course, on this on this
on this criminality of Brennan back in
2011.
So
so so there's that connection that's
been made and it's critical for you to
understand that, Michael, as well. But
if we fast forward a little bit, I want
to get into this little bit. If we fast
forward, Patrick Byrne, if anyone's been
following Patrick Byrne,
Svetlana Lokhova is somebody that I've
tried to reach out to because she's
tweeting about John Brennan daily. Now,
she was smeared
out of Cambridge with uh Stephen Halper,
uh John
and another guy named Sir Richard
Dearlove. Um that was the Russian
collusion uh with with General Michael
Flynn.
Svetlana and Flynn supposedly had
unnecessary relations, inappropriate
relations. That was because Flynn Flynn
was caught in that because he was
communicating with Moscow at the time.
That all comes back to what's called
Hamilton 68 dashboard, which is new
since the last time you and I spoke,
Michael. Hamilton 68 dashboard was was
it was a tech
facade
created for to create Russian bots on
Twitter. And that was supposedly what
was pumping up Trump and helped steal
the election
for Trump in 2016. This is this is what
John Brennan was driving home with the
Steele dossier. Okay?
And and that set a precedent and as the
two of you know, I spent a week and a
half in DC back in October passing out
100 copies of this book to various
offices of both the the House and the
Senate.
I had a few different meetings
and
and and if anybody seen that viral clip
with Nancy Pelosi where she's scolding
She told this Lindell TV reporter to
shut up. That was literally That was
like 10 minutes after I walked past her
in the hall out of Harriet Hagman's
office with John Donovan.
And I handed I handed her office a copy.
I'd given her office her office a copy.
I didn't hand it to Nancy, but I gave
her a copy of this book.
So we have this we have this John
Brennan narrative that I think is also
critical to understand. Why would he Why
would he What would give him motive? And
this is what I've told the staffers of
Congress. What would give him motive to
drive that Steele dossier? Well, the
contents in High Stakes Treason. The
fact that he's committed very serious
financial crimes. He's committed very
serious alleged treasonous crimes on the
American people. The contents in High
Stakes Treason is why he would have
orchestrated and spearheaded the the
Russian collusion efforts
to keep to to try to try to smear
Donald Trump. And of course what we know
and I'll tie this in real quickly give
give you guys a chance to
talk. Tie this in real quickly because
in 2020, that election we know was
stolen flat out. That's it was stolen.
John Brennan, it's something I've told
Michael, it's something I've told John
recently.
And I don't know if you looked at it at
all more, John, but but John Brennan
created a data center in Belgrade,
Serbia with Huawei, the Chinese software
company.
And that data center was used to
manipulate Dominion servers
to rig and adjust the results of that
2020 election. Now, why is it important
that Maduro was was arrested and
captured now in US custody? Because that
is how he retained power was through the
invention of Smartmatic, which he which
he created out from Hugo Chavez. This
Smartmatic was a Venezuelan voter fraud
voting system to to to basically
implement and place a communist leader
into offices. This is how Maduro was
captured. This is unfortunately why Tina
Peters Peters is locked up in in in
Colorado. And that is in my view, it's
not oil. Yeah, it's part of it. The drug
trading, trend Delaware,
are all part of it, but the main
critical point in capturing Maduro was
was was was was was to get at hopefully
what seems to be oncoming testimony in
regards to the
Dominion voter fraud.
And so John Brennan, as we as we listen
to this and he's now 70, John Brennan is
critical. He's a critical piece to this
to this to this voter fraud and this is
the other side to the coin outside of
the book. But if we go back again,
what would give him incentive? In from
my argument, non-legal
opinion, what would give him incentive
to drive that Steele dossier and and
fabrication? Well, because he's got he's
got he's got a demons in his closet and
and they're very serious.
Mhm.
Yeah, you know, and
a lot of other points in your book. One
of the two really stood out to me was
like you just said earlier,
uh Brennan had control over everything
in intelligence. And he kept that uh
from the FBI and they could have stopped
9/11.
And I was like, what? I was like, wow.
And and probably for profit, probably
for, you know, not just for himself, but
of course, but uh for the military
industrial complex. Who knows? Maybe
that's who was controlling him and
putting putting him in these positions
along with Obama.
Yeah, and and and on that note there,
Michael, which is very interesting and
John's already mentioned the George
Tenet aspect. And of course, both of you
have worked in the CIA, you would know
the machinations inside the CIA far
better than I would.
But one of the things that came to my
came to my attention was a testimonial
back in 2004 and I think it was Cynthia
McKinney, a guy named Michael Springmann
who was a State Department worker that
was working in Jeddah. He stated This is
two decades ago. He was stating he
returned to the US and he says, "Wait a
second, I get to Jeddah and 80 or 90% of
the people are CIA.
You know, there's only three State
Department at this embassy, only State
Department people." What he later says
in that testimonial, and Mike Benz has
reported on this, is that under the John
Brennan jurisdiction, 15
15 of the 19 9/11 hijacker visas came
out of that John Brennan jurisdiction in
Saudi Arabia. Exactly. Wow.
Unbelievable. Yeah. So So this is So
this this then
this then again and and remember that
key phrase for viewers is
counterterrorism intel monopoly. That is
the allegation that John Brennan created
for himself to hide this critical
information in what were called covert
compartments. So the question then
becomes is what did George Tenet know,
as you alluded to, Mike uh Michael, what
did George Tenet know
prior to the 9/11 attack? Well, we know
is that information was sequestered,
vital information was sequestered, just
as in that Boston Marathon bombing uh
regarding the Tsarnaev brothers and
where they were and where their
whereabouts were. Uh vital information
was was was hidden from uh critical
intelligence people, honest intelligent
people, patriotic intelligent people uh
that could have very well prevented um
prevented those attacks. So although we
although we we analyzed a three of three
of those three attacks, two
domestically, one on a NATO ally, um
my next my next move is to get in a
little bit more to to to as you talk
about uh is is uh is 9/11.
Um but uh anyway, so that's that's kind
of the current thought thoughts I have.
John.
Yeah. I
>> [laughter]
>> I mean
and we've we've lost you in the
darkness. Yeah, I apologize.
I as as we're talking, I'm re-scanning a
copy of the book and there's just so
much
it You know what?
Let's let's let's talk about it this
way, too. Let's say you are
you are a member of the political left.
Okay? Yeah. I don't I'm not talking
about a DNC Democrat, an MSNBC Democrat.
I'm talking about somebody who's truly
from the political left. Somebody from
the political left should be as
outraged as we are
that
any of this has taken place in the first
place.
Right?
>> Yeah, that's absolutely right. Look, in
my view, and this is why this is why I
mentioned very earlier Zbigniew
Brzezinski. Pardon me. Zbigniew
Brzezinski. Uh this is a What is he
Secretary of State? Was Is that right
under under
>> No, he was uh National Security Advisor
under Jimmy Carter.
National Security Advisor under Carter.
Um yeah, this is this is an apparatus as
as we as we as we as we kind of analyze,
right, the movement of where the country
has gone the last let's just say after
World War II because that was a very
critical juncture on the uh on the
global landscape of how uh
just how the world operates. Um if if if
we're looking at that broader spectrum,
we're looking at the red wave,
McCarthyism, and and we know that
communism has lurked in the background.
Oh, we're seeing it we're seeing it in
our face now. It's been We're being
slapped around with it now. With
Mondaire, right? This guy getting uh the
the the knife being pulled on an NYPD
officer NYPD
NYPD officer pulls the trigger on the
gun um and and Mondaire's calling for no
charges. I mean, are you kidding me? And
you've got yeah in Minneapolis this
these ridiculous people uh that are
saying, "No, we don't want you want ICE
out." Wait a second, ICE is there to
attack criminals that came in under, you
know, these open border policies that
invaded our country. Um yet you know,
the the very uh liberal-leaning
uh people in Minneapolis are are calling
it an ICE invasion and the you know,
Nazis and whatnot. I mean, this is this
is all these are all socialist tactics,
communist tactics that that we are now
in in Seattle Seattle's got a mayor
that's an open socialist uh that are
that are that are again, I'll use this
phrase, slapping us now in the face. So
they have lurked in the background being
the communist movement. Again, remember
John Brennan voting for the communist
candidate for mayor and
president 1976, Gus Hall. Um in my view,
uh John Brennan, I've never met him and
I've and I've and I've asked him to
comment on the book, he hasn't commented
on the book. I've tagged him on a number
of posts on Twitter, he hasn't hasn't
commented. The Daily Mail tried to reach
out to him and uh he didn't respond. Uh
and and that's actually why the Daily
Mail told me they couldn't release the
article.
Um the the the reporter spent 3 days
working on it. Um uh but uh but but but
my my my my guess, guys, my guess is
that uh the deep state, as we as as we
work as Americans, as patriots, as
constitutional Republicans, whether
we're Democrats or not, we're all
constitutional Republicans, we live in a
constitutional republic. That's what I
mean by that. Um
uh
we all look we all we all uh strive, I
think, anyway, at least the three of us
do, in chipping away and understanding
at what that deep state is. And that is
why I mentioned Lord Mandelson because
there's a lot of ties here to to the UK.
US and UK intelligence share share share
share a lot of ties. And this is why I
also mentioned uh Stephen Halper, who's
a CIA asset uh that worked uh at with
Cambridge University and and their their
surveillance programs uh that created
that Steele dossier. Let's not forget
the Steele dossier. Uh
Christopher Steele was a former former
and
UK intelligence asset, right? So we're
you know, we're we're we're we're trying
to keep a president out of office based
off of a foreign uh intelligence
uh
uh report or dossier. Um so as we chip
away to understand what that what that
uh what that what that deep state is, I
believe that this John Brennan uh person
was used as uh and I'll phrase it as a
penetration agent.
Uh a com- You know, he was a communist
sympathizer and I think he was probably
used uh to lay down certain structure in
the intelligence community that would
benefit that uh that outside uh deep
state um
uh organization.
Just my thought there. That's just my
thought. But again, looking through the
contents of High Stakes Treason, looking
through that it gives a re- gives the
reader a full understanding of how this
mind worked um how this mind worked to
build this intelligence monopoly
um to hide the information uh from the
American people, from critical
intelligence
operatives within our own
uh uh
agencies, um and and allow uh basically
what looks like the deep state to get
away with um their objectives. And I'll
identify two of them uh that people
should be considering
uh that are watching this. One, of
course, are our First Amendment rights.
Uh those different freedoms are always
under attack. Uh but if we look at the
history of Mao Zedong and what happened
in China, we look at Stalin, uh if we're
looking at Hitler, we're looking at
these different socialist uh
sympathizers that rose to power over
over the past century,
uh what were what was the common thread?
And this directs right back uh to uh and
I don't know the history of Zbigniew
Brzezinski enough, but it certainly goes
back to the philos- political
philosophies of of Barack Obama. Um this
goes right back to you've got to disarm
you've got to disarm the people, right?
In order to objectively gain complete
and total control, uh you've got to
disarm that those people. And that's
exactly what happened uh uh in China
over the over the decades of Mao Mao
Zedong's
uh uh rule. Is I think he's
uh some of the statist- statistics I've
seen is that he uh he slaughtered 60
million Chinese over his efforts to
confiscate private ownership of guns.
Um so uh you know, it's not that I'm uh
suggesting any type of violence. Nobody
wants violence and that's not something
I anyone as well. But an objective here
under the Obama administration using a
man like a John Brennan, a communist
sympathizer, would be efforts to chip
away at those Second Amendment rights in
in my view.
>> [clears throat]
>> Now, as far as like the uh the communist
aspect of it, you know, you mentioned
Mondaire and Danny
uh and of course Brennan.
Uh there's in the Epstein files, there's
uh
they just came out where Mondaire
Danny's mom is with and with him as a
baby is with Clinton and Epstein. And
some people are saying that uh Epstein
is Mondaire Danny's
father.
And uh so how did Mondaire Danny, who
came from nowhere,
no background, get all the way to the
mayor of, you know, one of the most
prestigious and up upstanding cities in
America, New York? No, he he didn't he
didn't have no background.
He had he was a uh
he was a city councilman and um and a
member of the New York State
Legislature.
So he did have a little bit of
background. Oh, yeah. Okay.
Yeah.
But what what else is interesting here
and I'll just I'll just kind of throw
this out for you you guys to to react uh
in in a way you might possibly have. And
and Michael, I have seen those photos. I
haven't confirmed them
uh that that
that Mondaire Danny's mother, and let's
not forget that Mondaire Danny, I
believe he's born in
uh Uganda,
uh
um that she she was hobnobbing. I think
there's one right there, Myra Herr.
I don't know I haven't confirmed that
they're it does or accurate or not with
Epstein
uh and that he would have been
introduced
uh Mondaire Danny would have been
introduced to uh to Epstein and or if
Epstein was was the father. I haven't
confirmed any of those, but I have seen
uh I have seen photos that show that
Mondaire Danny's wife or mother
allegedly was with was with Epstein. But
something interesting is this, as we
look at dominoes that may may fall.
Uh and John, I know some of the people
that you're you're you're talking to uh
right now. As we look at dominoes that
that that that fall as what caught my
interest in my interest in and Chris
Paronto if either of you familiar with
him, he's a former guest on my podcast
and he was directly involved in that
Benghazi massacre where Stevens was was
killed.
You know, this is this is under Hillary
Clinton's
time.
As I think it was the Secretary of
State, right?
If I've got that right. Um
it was interesting how this gentleman
and I don't know the name right now, but
this gentleman So just a few days ago,
right? And again, we're looking at
dominoes falling and how things might
happen on a global stage.
A few days ago the Clintons They agreed
to be to to to be in that
deposition. Uh with Comer
led by Comer.
And lo and behold now what 24 48 hours
later,
the Patel is now arrested and
Bondi the DOJ has arrested this guy
regard in regard to that Benghazi
fiasco. So the question I might have and
I'll pose it to both you guys cuz you
have intel minds that I don't have. Um
the question I might have is
what did the Clinton what did the
Clintons know about Benghazi? It may not
relate to Epstein at all or it may
relate to Epstein. I don't know.
I do know this which is very interesting
I'll mention that. When I was in New
York last and John if you remember the
panel discussion that we had
by by my literary agent Doug Doug. Um
after that I walked I walked down the
east side
with the gentleman who had walked me
right past Epstein's house. I'd never
seen it before.
And he says he says this is this is the
the Epstein mansion and Harrison and it
just so happens to be like a block away
from where the Council on Foreign
Relations offices. I don't know if you
looked at the Council on Foreign
Relations at all what that is what that
has been historically set up basically
by JP Morgan and and and the Rothschild.
Uh but but if we go we go back to this
gentleman that has been arrested in
Benghazi, does that correlate and could
that correlate not to get away from John
Brennan, but could that correlate to
what the Clintons might be might be
let's just say hiding from the American
people. And
more importantly Hillary Clinton.
No, Hillary Clinton testified for 14
hours about Benghazi.
And um
and
both Obama and Trump one ordered all the
Benghazi documents to be declassified.
They're all they're all out there. I
think Benghazi's over and done with.
It's great that we caught this Bactush
or whatever his name is today. He's he's
the third of the six primary
perpetrators of of the the murders at
Benghazi. I think there are 18 or 19
people altogether who have been
indicted. But uh
yeah, he he landed at Andrews Air Force
Base at 3:00 this morning. He's in the
Alexandria
federal federal holding right now. Yeah.
He's never going to see the light of
day.
Mhm. And and we're not done hunting
those the rest of them down.
I see. And gentlemen, you have to
forgive me. I have I have another uh
another
podcast in less than 1 minute. So I have
>> Okay, you got to go. I apologize. No
worries. Thanks, John.
>> Thanks for the conversation.
Yeah.
So Ian, it's
you know, I
I was there in Benghazi
shortly after that attack and uh
it was it was pretty bad because you
know, two of my buddies were were killed
in the mortar that landed on the roof.
Uh and I got you know, some of their
body armor that was bloody and all that
kind of stuff and got it got it back to
some certain people. But I
I didn't feel that Hillary Clinton
herself
was culpable
other than you know, maybe they could
have allowed
you know, some
like the Marines or the Marines are on
standby in that area
in the Mediterranean. There's jets that
could have came in all kind of crazy
stuff uh
and they they they basically shut them
down. Uh that's the story that I got. So
they could have come in and made a
difference and the guys that were there
at that base you know, fought fought off
guys that were trying to attack them for
a long time. Uh and and then they got
martyred.
So
I think there's
there's probably you could probably find
some problems with them and they wanted
to cover it up so that Obama could get
reelected. That's my thoughts.
Uh there there's probably some stuff
that could come out and make them not
look as good. Uh but as far as like you
know, direct culpability, I don't think
there's anything there.
I don't I don't think she's going to get
you know, like John said, she testified
for you know, a long time and
uh and you know, she made that that
very very bad statement was like why why
does anyone care now? You know, it's
like it's like really? So it's
it's they're just bad people, you know,
all the way around. Of course, they they
started all of that in Egypt with the
with the
was it Muslim Brotherhood that was in
Egypt?
Uh
that they were basically you know,
backing and took over Egypt.
You remember?
Yeah, I don't recall.
So
maybe not the Muslim Brotherhood, but
whatever sect that was there in Egypt
that took over
they were behind that and then the the
Egyptians basically kicked kicked them
out after after a year.
So there's there's they they were
messing around in you know, the Middle
East quite a bit
and causing a lot of problems.
The the Iran you know, thing there there
I guess Obama was like you know,
everybody should you know, revolt and
and that's what happened with
you know, Benghazi and everything and
that we're we're going to see I think a
big push back at some point that they
were involved in some stuff that I mean
you're you're in your high stakes trees
and you're
you know,
bringing out all kind of great stuff.
But we'll probably see Obama you know,
tied in with Brennan as well on a on a
on a level that's treasonous. What are
your thoughts?
Oh, my my thoughts are absolutely.
There's
there's there's there's there's there's
an overlaying
to me it's like there's an overlaying
theme of um we go from Clintons to
Bushes
then Obama and then it's like
you know, all all of those
uh
factions they were so opposed, right?
They were just so opposed to to Donald
Trump. He's a complete outsider. He's
going to expose, right? He's going to
expose the criminality is going to
spread expose the scheme that's being
the the wool. He's going to pull the
wool uh off
from the Americans Americans eyes. I
mean and that's basically how he's been
treated. He's been a complete outsider
and
and he's you know, he's he's he's a
warrior in there trying to get trying to
trying to get things done. But of
course, you've got this this theme of
okay, how far how do these connections
go? As certainly Epstein you don't have
any involvement doesn't look like any
involvement with Obama in the Epstein in
Epstein, but um in having John said he'd
come across that connection with
Brennan and that in Epstein, but he
didn't really
go into that much. Um
uh
my my guess is Michael my guess is
this this book uh because of the
contents of it because it exposes this
manipulation of critical national
intelligence uh by a very trusted uh
leader for the country.
Um
that as as it continues to circulate um
that that it will have some very
uh
devastating effects I believe on on this
kind of deep state uh
mechanism that has strangled strangled
uh the life of of of the constitutional
republic of the country.
And and that's certainly my goal
is that if anyone has committed crimes
uh that they be held accountable for the
crimes. It's you know, it's not that I
have a
it's not that I have a target uh to go
after John Brennan because you know, I I
don't like him as a person or he crossed
me wrong or I worked for him and he
didn't treat me well.
I I I never met him. I've never spoken
to him. I'm not that frankly I have
nothing nothing against the guy.
Um but the information that was
presented towards me
shows me from my vetting that he has
committed treasonous crimes on on the
country and he needs to be brought to
justice for those crimes or at least
a courtroom needs to be
needs to be analyzing them and and he
needs to be testifying in regards to the
contents. So
I have since you and I spoke last an
update here as I have spoken through a
text with Mike Davis. He's
head of Article 3 Project in in
Washington D.C. He's also working right
now with Jason Kinyones who's I believe
the lead attorney
for that South Florida subpoena of Jim
Jordan
that Jim Jordan
letter that came that went to the DOJ
requesting he be subpoenaed.
And so now he's his lawyers are working.
They're trying to change change the
jurisdiction. Brennan hasn't been in the
in in the news for a couple of weeks
now, but
my understanding is his lawyers have
been trying to change that jurisdiction.
That's Fort Fort Pierce
court uh, Judge Cannon. The same judge,
by the way, that, uh, that, that, that,
that just sentenced uh, Ryan Rout and
interesting thing that that I'll also
mention, I don't know how much time you
got left here, but the interesting
thing, Michael, that that has, uh, come,
uh,
my way is a Mike Benz, uh,
report back in August. And he compared,
uh, Ryan Rout, who he claims and shows
that he Rout was a CIA asset, uh,
recruiting Pakistani and Iranian, uh,
men to join and fight in Ukraine.
And, um, and he was asking for
passports, okay, bring up passports
again, asking for passports so he could
submit, administer, uh, visas, uh, get
visas authorized for these people to go
and fight in Ukraine. Well, this is the
same act that the CIA was doing,
uh,
in the early 2000s, uh, or or late 19,
1990s,
uh, to get those, uh, 15 hijackers,
uh, in into the US. Um,
I mean, it's it's it's This is pretty
critical, right? This is pretty critical
information. And again, that's
testimony. Not my testimony, it's
testimony from this, uh, former State
Department worker, Michael Springmann.
So, I think as this, as the contents of
this book circulate and push, and
hopefully Mike Davis gets involved with
it, perhaps, uh, hopefully Mr. John
Brennan uh, gets back in a courtroom and
he's not only subpoenaed for the lies
that he gave, uh, the perjury, um, uh,
indicted, I would say, uh, at that
point, hopefully,
uh, for the perjury charges against him,
uh, that I would assume should be coming
down uh, to Congress, but that he be
questioned questioned regarding the
contents of this book because this is
what's plain as day, Michael. This is
what's plain as day. Is that in SEC
documents we show this. In what's called
the ethics waiver. And nothing in this
book is classified. This is all, uh,
open sourced. It's all, uh, public
information. It's just that it was
aggregated by the appropriate source to
be able to combine it and it's been
delivered to the to the to the public
and in the masses through me. Um, is
that, uh, is that that nine 2009 ethics
waiver by Norm Eisen. We see very
clearly, uh, the Rachel Maddow, uh,
who's the office ethics office officer,
she writes on that ethics waiver that
John Brennan has stated that he would be
converting those stocks held in the
analysis corporation into a four, uh,
into an IRA. If I were to held in a
401k, it'd be converted in an IRA. We
see through subsequent SEC documents,
uh, we have some of them listed in the
appendix, uh, in that book, that, uh, he
never converted the that the those
stocks into the IRA. Had he converted
them, that they would have been
liquidated, uh, worth then about
$50,000. Um, he didn't convert them and,
uh, it rose to when the when when when
that company sold, it rose to a value of
as we estimate just shy of $5 million.
And that is just one example of the
illegally illegally held stocks. And
this is going to be irrefutable. It's
going to be impossible, from my vetting,
it's going to be impossible for him to,
uh, refute that. Uh, we have we have we
have it laid out in the book. Um, these
are massive crimes this man has
committed, financial crimes. Um, and the
other crimes, uh,
are are something else,
uh, but, uh, but potentially this
individual, uh, could be facing, uh,
many years,
uh, of justice. Uh, and it's it's only
my job again to, uh, to to to educate
the American people to do that. And
again, what I will say, Michael, is we
we've got it We've all got to go through
the contents of the book. Uh, we've all
got to study it. We've all got to read
it. Got to get our neighbors talking
about it. Buy buy a copy for for your
co-worker, um, and don't let it stop
there. Demand demand that this man be
held accountable for the criminality.
Um, cuz if we don't all contact, that
means contacting the DOJ. That means
contacting your senator. Contacting your
rep. Um,
uh, demanding that this this person be
held accountable for the crimes. And if
we don't all do that, then, uh, you
know, it's it comes back to to people
like me, the author, people like you,
uh, people like John, um, and and we
can't rely on just us. It It needs It
needs more people. Now, I know that
John, um, because he's been very
outspoken recently, uh, of how he was
treated, um,
he's he's spoken to some some pretty,
uh, high level folks recently.
Whether he's shared that with you or
not, um, uh,
just out of confidentiality with John
and information he's passed along to me,
um, he didn't go into it with in this in
this episode. Um, and that was maybe a
personal decision or maybe because he
wasn't asked the question, I don't know,
but in confidentiality I won't go into
it, but I know that he's spoken with
some pretty high level folks recently.
Um,
yeah, I mean, we we we keep pushing and
and and and we keep making strides. But
for viewers out there and listeners, and
Michael, what I will say is this, after
the last time you and I spoke, uh,
couple days later I get a text from
Roger Stone. Uh, and Roger Stone says,
"Hey, uh, people have been contacting me
because they saw the Michael Jaco
interview. Great interview."
>> [laughter]
>> Awesome. Awesome.
Yeah. Yeah, I I Yeah, I love Roger. He
hits his work and you know, what, you
know, he's another one that, you know,
uh, had a lot of pressure and, you know,
has,
you know, gone to jail and all that kind
of stuff. So, uh, this is chapter three.
I I brought up your Kindle version. I
have the I have the, uh, audio, too.
Uh, and you're talking about how Brennan
Brennan's former boss, CIA Director
George Tenet, despite his failure to
prevent 9/11, I mean, we have the best
intel sources in the world and we
couldn't, you know, stop 9/11? That to
me was like that was a big red flag to
me. Uh, and so it sounds like these a
lot of these guys are corrupt. And
you're you're kind of pointing this out
in the book as well. It's not just
Brennan, but we have, uh, probably a
long list of these guys that, you know,
uh, you know, support each other and,
uh, you know, make each other help each
other get become rich. George Tenet
cashes in on Iraq. Former CIA chief is
earning big money from corporations
profiting off the war.
So, this seems to be, uh,
a trend in the CIA. I can tell you from
my experience this is, uh, this is
accurate.
Yeah, I know. I mean, this is this is
something that I had mentioned, uh,
yesterday, uh, with, uh, a guy named,
uh, Paul Paul Hollar, uh,
excuse me, Paul Harel, H A R R E L L.
Um, and his and his podcast
is, um,
is is is What is George Tenet know? You
know, what did what did he know
that he that he's still hiding to this
day? Absolutely. Uh,
that could have, uh,
that could prevented uh, those attacks.
Now,
um,
Operation Northwoods is something that I
that I've mentioned in the past. Yeah,
very good. Uh,
because this is That was something that
John F. Kennedy, they wanted him to do
it and he was like, "No way." And then
they killed him, of course. They just
dusted off and brought it out again.
That's what this total same thing.
Yeah, that's exactly right. That's
exactly right. And, um, and and it looks
like again, and this is why I mentioned
the shadow, the communist movement in
the shadows that have been lurking
through the decades because objectively
what do they want to do? Well, the first
thing is destabilize the union and
they're doing a good job of it,
unfortunately, right now.
Um, you fractionalize it, you you pit
you you create this dialectic, you
create a left and a right that that that
that that, you know, pitted against each
other, um, because because as we know,
uh,
divided divided we, uh,
we fall. Uh, that's just the way it is.
Um,
in in a in a union you objective, of
course, is to
break to to weaken the union.
Um, they're doing that and then you chip
away at those constitutional rights. Um,
and, um, and and if you and you can do
that and you can lurk in the background,
I mean, here's a here's something else I
always consider is, uh, you know, we are
we're we're not even yet 250 years old
as a as a as a nation. Uh, you have
monarchs in Europe that are, you know,
that are triple that. Um, you have, uh,
as an example, the United Kingdom, uh,
which is, uh, subservient and we spoke
to this earlier last time, uh,
subservient The monarchy is subservient
to Londinium, which is known as London
today. It's a Roman banking center. Uh,
this is, uh,
uh, this is, uh, William of William the
Conqueror, 1066, that conquered the
British Isles, but didn't conquer
Londinium, uh, and the Lord Mayor, which
controls the monarchy. The Charles or
the Queen, uh, they don't they don't
control London. London controls it. And
that's that's just this is this is very
important to understand these empirical,
uh,
structures,
uh, that that are still in play and and
I always argue that control our own
financial system and our own federal
government. We're we're we're not quite
as free as we think we are financially.
We are we we have our military and it's
the most impressive on the on the planet
I've ever seen and we have our
geographic country, but we don't we
don't have our economic independence and
that's not, you know, it doesn't take a,
uh, third grader to see that, um,
because you got a $36 trillion federal
deficit, you know, why why doesn't that
ever get paid off? Um, but, uh, but
again, I I believe the deep state is
this communist apparatus lurking in the
backgrounds in the shadows slowly
grinding and slowly chipping away. And
if it takes them 200 years, it takes
them 200 years. Again, their families
have been in power for far longer than
that. Uh, so if it's their
great-grandchildren that are finally
able to to destroy the the US. But
another critical component of that and
when I was addressing Dominion servers,
we can look at USAID and the money
funded and and and I was given a graph a
couple weeks ago of how, uh, USA AID
money was funding Dominion servers. And
that that means basically you're set up
by the United Nations, uh, which I
question greatly. You're set up
basically by the United Nations
in a in a in a in a such a sophisticated
manner
intellectually that you're committing
you're committing national suicide. What
I mean by that is the United States is
is is funding of course voter fraud.
That right? Because you're funding USAID
and they're you're turning around and
funding
the municipal voter fraud. Then
you're you're killing yourself
basically. And why are you doing that?
Because you're not catching
you're not catching the fraud that
that's happening. What we have here with
high stakes treason is a great
opportunity
to take down a critical
player in that deep state mechanism. And
if we can take him down those dominoes
are going to fall.
And and I firmly believe that we can if
we collectively come together and we and
we do this and we
exhort this effort we can take this
individual out. And I agree.
Yeah.
And if people like Stone and Kari Lake
aren't going to aren't going to hurt us
or
they're going to help. Yeah, there's
there's so much and you revealed so much
information on him Ian that's it's just
it's phenomenal and people read the book
and they'll they'll see for themselves
like I and John you know both part of
the CIA for a good number of years and
we read your book and we're like what?
We didn't know some of the stuff that
you pointed out. And you have excellent
resources and references and so forth.
So people can
like I had one of one of I had one of
them up. I just click on it in the the
Kindle version and it pulls it right up.
It's like it's fantastic. So really
really nice job on the book and
revealing so fant-
I think it's going to be one of those
things that basically you know is the
it's going to
it's going to push him off. Push him off
his ped- at all pedestal and then
they'll they'll they'll they'll be able
to take him down.
So we getting involved we the American
people you know reading this and and
demanding justice.
Yeah, absolutely. Exactly that's exactly
right.
Let me just quickly revisit that that
comment that I was making in regards to
George Tenet and that line that you
wrote that you that you read
in the book is that people need to of
course question the that was not a raw
terror attack that was designed
engineered attack and why was it done?
It was to create this whole homeland
security apparatus this whole war on
terror and and and not to forget the
Brennan crimes in the book were
allegedly done during the war on terror
that meant providing aid and comfort to
an enemy during a war that is the global
war on terror. And that is another
reason why in the subject of the book
the title of the book
word treason is used.
Again, if you successfully engineer
and perform this 9/11 feat then that is
creating again
the war on terror and that is used to
break down those those constitutional
rights. In
a in a in a in a engineered you know two
decade plan slowly right? It's slowly
slowly slowly done. But but that's going
to be my my next
kind of effort is to dig into what
George Tenet may have known and and and
the book is certainly not there.
Very good very very good. And I I
completely agree with you you know
having been part of that for over 20
years.
And
all of us almost all of us down range
are like why are these wars going keep
going on? Because we could we could have
crushed this in 6 months to a year. Why
are we still here in like in Afghanistan
for over 20 years? It's insane. I mean
World War IV or two rather
was over in four years you know four or
five years and so we're in Afghanistan a
little p dunk country for over 20 years.
It's insane. So it's obviously major
manipulation that's going on.
Yeah, and I think
not to not to segue too much and I can
send you this graph but there's
there's these connections called it's I
think the title of the graph and it's
it's maybe 30 pages long. It's saying
this the silk the third silk road or
something like that. A lot of what was
happening and what continues to happen
in Afghanistan has to do with relations
with the pharmaceutical industry and and
China and those that control the control
that in those industries
but that's that's a whole other topic to
get into. And I think I'll I'll shoot
that over to you Michael you can take a
peek at that. Yeah, appreciate that.
Thanks a lot.
So your book it's on
it's on Amazon where else can that
people get your book High Stakes
Treason? Yeah, I mean I I would I would
suggest ordering it from me directly
helps my effort out a little bit more.
I'm happy to send out a signed copy.
You can Venmo me send you send send send
you out a signed copy. I just sent
three copies out couple days ago
but Amazon certainly the easiest way.
Leave a review. That helps
with with the ranking
and and know that I'm I'm hoping I'm
hoping to
to have a a second edition by July July
22nd would be the one year anniversary.
I'm hoping not not not committing to
that. No guarantees but that's my hope
is because there's so much more
development Michael going on in regards
to the John Brennan cover-up and and
voter fraud with his Dominion what he
knew about General Flynn and and these
different things. So
so there's all all of those types of
topics will
Okay, great.
And in the second edition. They can get
your book at High Stakes Treason is that
correct?
Yeah, highstakes treason.com should come
up. You might have to type in https.
Did it come up when you popped it into
the search engine there just high stakes
treason?
It wants to go to Amazon but uh
see if I see it in here. I had it last
show so I'll find it and make sure I put
it in the um
description box.
Awesome man. Yeah.
High Stakes Treason and and I and I what
I do is I upload all interviews
interviews
to that website. They go to the I think
it's media appearances
and then and then the home page the
landing page for that website goes into
some nice detail of the exact crimes
that that I allege were committed and
and what needs to happen. What
we can do
in regards to in regards to reclaiming
some of our sovereignty back from from
from
John Brennan what he what he's done and
and doing to the country. So there's
some critical information there on that
home page as well.
Yeah, very good. And I I did find that
so let me let me share it on the screen.
I put it in the chat and then I'll put
it in the description box as well. So
Yeah, this this got great information.
And uh
there's lots of links in here that you
can uh
get in media appearances about the
author book overview. So lots of really
good stuff press kit. So if you want to
you know have Ian on your show out there
so I I recommend it cuz as you guys can
see
he has incredible amount of information.
So
Ian thanks so much for coming on once
again.
Uh great
great show. Thanks for being John on he
was amazing. So keep keep revealing.
We're going to keep doing it till we get
this guy put away.
That's good. All right, talk soon.
All right.